eolss.net 2018-01-02

# Encyclopedia of Life Support Systems - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy Statement

THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES SOLELY TO THE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE WHILE VISITING THE EOLSS-ONLINE WORLDWIDE WEB SITE. THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY DO NOT GOVERN PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION FURNISHED THROUGH ANY MEANS OTHER THAN THE EOLSS-ONLINE SITE.

UNESCO-Encyclopedia of Life Support Systems(EOLSS) recognize the importance of protecting the information it collects in the operation of EOLSS-Online and will take all reasonable steps to maintain security, integrity and privacy of this information.

## Storage of Information

UNESCO-Encyclopedia of Life Support Systems(EOLSS) will ensure that any information it collects will be adequate, relevant and not excessive for the purposes of operating EOLSS-Online; it will be kept accurate and up-to-date based on information provided and will be deleted when no longer needed. Except where necessary in connection with services provided by appropriate intermediaries, who will be required to comply with the confidentiality provisions of this policy, UNESCO-Encyclopedia of Life Support Systems(EOLSS) will not disclose any personal information identifying Authorized Users or the licensee to any third party, unless required by law or to enforce the Terms and Conditions. Certain personal information may be collected when you contact us with questions or offer feedback on the EOLSS-Online site.

We may use "cookies" to identify you and your access on the EOLSS-Online Site as well as recording usage of the EOLSS-Online Site. A cookie is a piece of information that is sent to your Web browser from a Website and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each time you return to the EOLSS-Online Site, we are able to identify you as a previous or registered visitor. Cookies also enable the traffic to the EOLSS-Online Site to be measured, including the number of user revisits versus new visitors, the time users spend on the Site, and their navigation behavior.

## Links to Other Sites

EOLSS-Online Site may contain links to other Web sites that are not under our control. Such other sites do not necessarily follow this Privacy Policy, and may place their own cookies on your computer. We do not control cookies placed on your computer by third parties.

## Use of Information

Information that we collect may be used: to contact you if follow-up communications are necessary, to notify you of services and offers, improve the EOLSS-Online Site, for development of new products and services, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes.

## Privacy Policy Inquiries

Inquiries regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to EOLSS-Online at [eolssunesco@gmail.com](mailto:eolssunesco@gmail.com)
